MAYURI SHATKUNARAJAH

Worked as an IT- Lecturer | Powercoders Participant

Wyde 20, 5242 Birr | 17.05.1986 | Residence permit B (Sri Lankan)

Married | 1 Son

mayuri.shatkunarajah@powercoders.org |078 329 81 23

GitHub | Learning Blog | Online portfolio

Languages: English (B2), German (B2), Tamil (mother tongue)

IT skills: Advanced: MS-Office.

Intermediate: Java, PHP, DBMS, Photoshop, Web design.

Elementary: C++, VB, ASP, Networking.

Beginner: Python.



I graduated with a Master degree in IT and am highly motivated, flexible and hardworking with 5 years of experience in IT as a lecturer. I'm seeking opportunities to utilize my skills in an IT Company that offers resourceful and innovative growth professionally.

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2015 – 01/2019 Housewife and Mother, Sri Lanka.

03/2014 – 08/2015 IT-Lecturer, College of Technology, Jaffna, Sri Lanka.

Teaching MS-Office, Networking, Programming languages, DBMS to NVQ

Level 4and 5.

07/2010 - 08/2014 IT-Lecturer (Part time), Private Institute Spectra Skills, Sri Lanka.

Teaching MS-Office, Photoshop, Web design, Programming languages.

03/2011 – 04/2012 IT-Lecturer, Private Institute IIS, Sri Lanka.

- Teaching MS-Office, Photoshop, Web design, Programming languages.

08/2010 – 02/2011 IT-Instructor, Private Institute Magnet, Teacher Training Program (ICDL)

- Teaching MS-Office.

EDUCATION

04/2021 – 07/2021 Powercoders – Coding Academy for Refugees, Zurich.

- Foundations in HTML, CSS, JavaScript; specialization tracks upcoming

- Weekly business & social skills training (team work, communication, etc.)

06/2007 – 11/2009 Master of Science in Information Technology, Bishop Heber College

(Bharathidasan university), India.

- Programming in C, C++, Java, ASP, DBMS, Computer Networks, Soft skills.

- Project: Transaction and recharge of Mobile using J2ME, Java Platform,

Technova solutions, India.

06/2004 – 04/2007 Bachelor of Science in Physics (Computer application), Periyar University, India.

Properties of matter, Electricity, Mechanics, Programming languages COBOL,

Pascal, C, C++.

CONTINUOUS EDUCATION

09/2020 – 02/202 German language course, Lingua Nova, B2.

06/2019 – 02/2020 German language course, AVS, B1.

HOBBIES

I enjoy reading books, designing and tailoring clothes, arts & crafts, dancing,

listening to music as well as yoga.

REFERENCES

Hussam Allaham Industry Lead, Powercoders Deutschschweiz,

hussam.allaham@powercoders.org, +41 77 906 16 27

Christophe

Gunzenhauser Head of Social Services, Social commission Birr.

christophe.gunzenhauser@birr.ch, +41 56 464 43 20